I have written a book titled Introduction to Networking,
How the Internet Works, that complements the material
in this Udemy course.
This book is available both in print and free online.
It has been translated into Spanish, Greek, and Russian.
One fun fact about the book is that all the figures
are drawn in a style called sketch note.
There are no words in the figures, only concepts.
This means that every translation of the book
can use the exact same artwork that was by design.
The book roughly covers the first two thirds of this course,
focusing on protocols, packets,
and layered network architecture.
It's designed to be an easy read and helpful companion
to the lectures and interviews throughout the course.
I've also created a simple speech-to-text audiobook
that you can listen to with any podcast application
or online, and I hope you find the book
a valuable addition to the class.
You'll find a link to the book's website and podcast
in the resources link associated with these lecture.
Welcome to the course, and I hope to see you online.
Cheers.